oskaya.com 2011-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Oskaya

Privacy Policy 

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all Oskaya including all the websites run under the **Oskaya.com**. Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our contact form.

In the case of possible copyright infringement please contact the responsible parties.

Oskaya operates as an index and database of anime content found publicly available on the Internet.  
Users who upload to these websites agree not to upload illegal content when creating their user accounts.  
Oskaya does not take responsibility for the content hosted on such third party websites.

Please Be informed That We DO NOT host any videos on this website, its broadcasted from people has been taken from 3rd party video sharing websites such as Youtube, Dailymotion, Metacafe, Veoh, Myspace, Justin TV, UStream, Freedocast and others and we have no relationship with the uploaders of videos. We just search for the video we’re looking for on Google and we embed video to our posts.

We are sensetive about copyright issues because we know that there is big effort by many people behind the work thats why we want you guys to contact us once you see that we violate your copyrights, simply send a mail to us stating the content URLs and then we will immediately delete the content and URLs.

Email Address

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. 

Comments/Message Boards

Most Oskaya Network websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

Advertising and Cookies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ads and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Traffic Reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded.

Legal proceedings

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Oskaya may need to disclose information when required by law.

Links

Oskaya websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Oskaya

Notification of Changes

When oskaya makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please **contact us** at **Admin[at]oskaya.com**
